Haha...so cute!
Yakanta Idol
The Blu-ray of Kashiwagi Hinatachan's graduation performance and the first live of the new organization will be released on March 29.
And on April 1, Musha Shugyo free live final will be held at Osaka Nanko ATC Seaside Stage.
We have been working hard on the lessons, so please come and see the show. And from April 15, Mayuna E Mayuna's first spring tour
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebizum will be held on May 3.
On May 3, Ebichu's first single in 4 years, "Kyodou" will be released. Please listen to it a lot. For more information, please check out the official Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku website.
Bye bye!
Bye bye! Last but not least, I would like to say to Ms. Nakamura
Last but not least, we would like to present you with an energizing cup of tea from our nightclub!
Here it is!
Bon appétit!
Yes, sir.
What's today's tea?
Today's tea is from Kagoshima, isn't it? It's Kagoshima tea, isn't it?
It's Kirancha.
Do you know it?
Kagoshima is said to be a great tea-growing area.
It is one of the best places in Japan.
I had never heard of it before.
You seem to be an honor student.
Do you love school and study very much?
I love studying.
It's different from the result, isn't it?
You are smart!
Wanderliker says.
I see.
Are you going in that direction, too?
Yes.
Oh, my God. God gives us all kinds of things, doesn't he?
Stardust, you know, legitimately everyone.
There's a little bit of the beautiful British thing going on here.
It's okay. Showing the new Stardads, and the seniors, too.
I know that many of them were a little bit like that.
I would like to ask you to lead them by all means.
Please give us a final, cute, closing message.
Please continue to know and support me a lot.
Yes, I will. I am Ayana Nakamura from Private Art Junior High School.
What is going on?
Surprisingly, you might be better at this job if you work hard and stay pretty until you are OK.
Please learn one thing and go home.
Yes, I will.
Thank you very much.
This program is for
Ms. Tokazuchan, Mr.
Mr. Shumai, Mr.
Mr. Taiga, Mr.
Yuni Aoi, and
and Ietenezo.
Thank you very much.